[{"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [2, 25, 26], "object_names": ["wall", "wall", "wall"], "question": "Is there a wall in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "Is there a rail in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "Is there a shelf in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [1], "object_names": ["ceiling"], "question": "Is there a ceiling in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["floor"], "question": "Is there a floor in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "Is there a counter in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "Is there a picture in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "Is there a rack in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [7, 13, 22, 23], "object_names": ["pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow"], "question": "Is there a pillow in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [10, 24], "object_names": ["sign", "sign"], "question": "Is there a sign in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a drum in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a bread in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a divider in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a basket in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a paper in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a air conditioner in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a pedestal in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a kitchen island in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a bar in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a window frame in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [10, 24], "object_names": ["sign", "sign"], "question": "How many signs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["floor"], "question": "How many floors are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["3"], "object_ids": [2, 25, 26], "object_names": ["wall", "wall", "wall"], "question": "How many walls are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "How many pictures are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "How many counters are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "How many rails are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "How many shelfs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "How many racks are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "How many tables are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "How many archs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [1], "object_names": ["ceiling"], "question": "How many ceilings are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["couch"], "question": "How many couchs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["4"], "object_ids": [7, 13, 22, 23], "object_names": ["pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow"], "question": "How many pillows are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["3"], "object_ids": [29, 30, 31], "object_names": ["case", "case", "case"], "question": "How many cases are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "How many keyboards are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["simple yet elegant, with a smooth, rounded form", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["serves as a focal point, dividing the space into two distinct areas"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["spans much of the height of the room", "Large"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["stone"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["simple yet elegant, with a smooth, rounded form", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is arch. Its material is stone. Its size is spans much of the height of the room. Its placement is positioned vertically at the center of the room. Its function is serves as a focal point, dividing the space into two distinct areas. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["spans much of the height of the room", "Large"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is arch. Its material is stone. Its shape is simple yet elegant, with a smooth, rounded form. Its placement is positioned vertically at the center of the room. Its function is serves as a focal point, dividing the space into two distinct areas. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["serves as a focal point, dividing the space into two distinct areas"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is arch. Its material is stone. Its size is spans much of the height of the room. Its shape is simple yet elegant, with a smooth, rounded form. Its placement is positioned vertically at the center of the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["positioned vertically at the center of the room", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["arch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is arch. Its material is stone. Its size is spans much of the height of the room. Its shape is simple yet elegant, with a smooth, rounded form. Its function is serves as a focal point, dividing the space into two distinct areas. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[0.21889115261265735, 0.5934631616922532, 2.4576610994338988, 0.6598321886318864, 6.75668, 4.88168, 1.963494830140332, 7.850462293418876e-16, -1.570092458683777e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["hung vertically in the central position on the wall", "Hanging"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["picture"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is picture. Its color is grayscale with hints of black and white. Its material is canvas. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hung vertically in the central position on the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is to decorate a room. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is picture. Its color is grayscale with hints of black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hung vertically in the central position on the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is to decorate a room. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["hung vertically in the central position on the wall", "Hanging"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is picture. Its color is grayscale with hints of black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is canvas. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is to decorate a room. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["picture"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is grayscale with hints of black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is canvas. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hung vertically in the central position on the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is to decorate a room. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["shelf"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["wood"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["stores books, files, and other items"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its color is white. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against a wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is stores books, files, and other items. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against a wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is stores books, files, and other items. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["stores books, files, and other items"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its color is white. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against a wall. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wood"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its color is white. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against a wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is stores books, files, and other items. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["provide support"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["vertically on the sofa, leaning against the backrest", "Leaning"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["soft"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["pillow"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is green and white. Its texture is soft. Its material is likely cotton or similar material. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on the sofa, leaning against the backrest. Its state is good condition, no signs of wear or damage. Its function is provide support. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["soft"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is green and white. Its material is likely cotton or similar material. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on the sofa, leaning against the backrest. Its state is good condition, no signs of wear or damage. Its function is provide support. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is green and white. Its texture is soft. Its material is likely cotton or similar material. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on the sofa, leaning against the backrest. Its state is good condition, no signs of wear or damage. Its function is provide support. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["vertically on the sofa, leaning against the backrest", "Leaning"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is green and white. Its texture is soft. Its material is likely cotton or similar material. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition, no signs of wear or damage. Its function is provide support. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["dark", "Black"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["serve as barriers or boundaries for safety or defining specific areas"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["vertically arranged on the wall, spanning across the horizontal line", "Hanging"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["metal or polished stone", "Stone"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["streamlined, slim", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is dark. Its texture is smooth. Its material is metal or polished stone. Its size is moderate. Its placement is vertically arranged on the wall, spanning across the horizontal line. Its state is good condition, no visible gaps between components. Its function is serve as barriers or boundaries for safety or defining specific areas. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["metal or polished stone", "Stone"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is dark. Its texture is smooth. Its size is moderate. Its shape is streamlined, slim. Its placement is vertically arranged on the wall, spanning across the horizontal line. Its state is good condition, no visible gaps between components. Its function is serve as barriers or boundaries for safety or defining specific areas. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["good condition, no visible gaps between components"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is dark. Its texture is smooth. Its material is metal or polished stone. Its size is moderate. Its shape is streamlined, slim. Its placement is vertically arranged on the wall, spanning across the horizontal line. Its function is serve as barriers or boundaries for safety or defining specific areas. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is dark. Its material is metal or polished stone. Its size is moderate. Its shape is streamlined, slim. Its placement is vertically arranged on the wall, spanning across the horizontal line. Its state is good condition, no visible gaps between components. Its function is serve as barriers or boundaries for safety or defining specific areas. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["holds red flowers"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["glass"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["upright on a wooden desk", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["upright on a wooden desk", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its material is glass. Its size is medium. Its function is holds red flowers. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is glass. Its size is medium. Its placement is upright on a wooden desk. Its function is holds red flowers. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its material is glass. Its placement is upright on a wooden desk. Its function is holds red flowers. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["glass"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its size is medium. Its placement is upright on a wooden desk. Its function is holds red flowers. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["vertical", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_25"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_26"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_27"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is sign. Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its size is moderate. Its shape is vertical. Its placement is fixed to wall with two screws. Its function is provides support for stability and safety. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is sign. Its color is black. Its size is moderate. Its shape is vertical. Its placement is fixed to wall with two screws. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support for stability and safety. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_25"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["fixed to wall with two screws", "Hanging"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is sign. Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its size is moderate. Its shape is vertical. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support for stability and safety. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_26"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["sign"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["sign"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its size is moderate. Its shape is vertical. Its placement is fixed to wall with two screws. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support for stability and safety. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_27"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_28"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_29"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["serving as the central element for storing and accessing writing tools"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_30"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_31"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["serving as the central element for storing and accessing writing tools"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its material is plastic. Its size is moderate-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is filled. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_28"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["moderate-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its material is plastic. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is filled. Its function is serving as the central element for storing and accessing writing tools. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_29"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its size is moderate-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is filled. Its function is serving as the central element for storing and accessing writing tools. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_30"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its material is plastic. Its size is moderate-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is filled. Its function is serving as the central element for storing and accessing writing tools. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_31"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["cotton or similar material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_32"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["square", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_33"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["pillow"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_34"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["providing support and comfort for people sitting on the sofa"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_35"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["square", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is beige. Its texture is soft. Its material is cotton or similar material. Its size is medium. Its placement is lying flat on the sofa. Its state is in good condition. Its function is providing support and comfort for people sitting on the sofa. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_32"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is beige. Its texture is soft. Its material is cotton or similar material. Its shape is square. Its placement is lying flat on the sofa. Its state is in good condition. Its function is providing support and comfort for people sitting on the sofa. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_33"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["providing support and comfort for people sitting on the sofa"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is beige. Its texture is soft. Its material is cotton or similar material. Its size is medium. Its shape is square. Its placement is lying flat on the sofa. Its state is in good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_34"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["lying flat on the sofa", "Lying flat"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is beige. Its texture is soft. Its material is cotton or similar material. Its size is medium. Its shape is square. Its state is in good condition. Its function is providing support and comfort for people sitting on the sofa. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_35"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standing upright on the white floor", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_36"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["metal or similar material", "Metal"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_37"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["square", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_38"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["smooth with visible marks"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_39"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["counter"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark-colored. Its texture is smooth with visible marks. Its material is metal or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is square. Its placement is standing upright on the white floor. Its function is serving as a functional bar or service area. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_36"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["metal or similar material", "Metal"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is counter. Its color is dark-colored. Its texture is smooth with visible marks. Its size is moderate. Its shape is square. Its placement is standing upright on the white floor. Its function is serving as a functional bar or service area. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_37"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing upright on the white floor", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is counter. Its color is dark-colored. Its texture is smooth with visible marks. Its material is metal or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is square. Its function is serving as a functional bar or service area. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_38"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is counter. Its color is dark-colored. Its texture is smooth with visible marks. Its material is metal or similar material. Its shape is square. Its placement is standing upright on the white floor. Its function is serving as a functional bar or service area. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_39"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_40"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standing upright on table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_41"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["glass, wood, artificial flowers, beads", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_42"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["decorative, adds warmth and countryside charm"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_43"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["glass, wood, artificial flowers, beads", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clear, red, white, yellow, green. Its texture is smooth. Its size is moderate. Its placement is standing upright on table. Its function is decorative, adds warmth and countryside charm. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_40"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clear, red, white, yellow, green. Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass, wood, artificial flowers, beads. Its placement is standing upright on table. Its function is decorative, adds warmth and countryside charm. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_41"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["clear, red, white, yellow, green", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass, wood, artificial flowers, beads. Its size is moderate. Its placement is standing upright on table. Its function is decorative, adds warmth and countryside charm. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_42"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["decorative, adds warmth and countryside charm"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clear, red, white, yellow, green. Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass, wood, artificial flowers, beads. Its size is moderate. Its placement is standing upright on table. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_43"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["green"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_44"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_45"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["paper"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_46"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_47"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["paper"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is green. Its texture is well-preserved. Its size is moderate. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. Its function is provides information and entertainment. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_44"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is green. Its texture is well-preserved. Its material is paper. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. Its function is provides information and entertainment. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_45"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["green"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is well-preserved. Its material is paper. Its size is moderate. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. Its function is provides information and entertainment. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_46"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is green. Its texture is well-preserved. Its material is paper. Its size is moderate. Its state is closed. Its function is provides information and entertainment. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_47"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["filled with various items"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_48"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["cylindrical with a wide opening at the top", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_49"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_50"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sits upright on a wooden table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_51"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["filled with various items"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass. Its size is just right. Its shape is cylindrical with a wide opening at the top. Its placement is sits upright on a wooden table. Its function is adds a touch of countryside charm to the overall environment and is an excellent decoration for any room. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [21], "output_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_48"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its material is glass. Its size is just right. Its shape is cylindrical with a wide opening at the top. Its placement is sits upright on a wooden table. Its state is filled with various items. Its function is adds a touch of countryside charm to the overall environment and is an excellent decoration for any room. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [21], "output_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_49"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass. Its size is just right. Its shape is cylindrical with a wide opening at the top. Its placement is sits upright on a wooden table. Its state is filled with various items. Its function is adds a touch of countryside charm to the overall environment and is an excellent decoration for any room. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [21], "output_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_50"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["just right", "Medium"], "object_ids": [21], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass. Its shape is cylindrical with a wide opening at the top. Its placement is sits upright on a wooden table. Its state is filled with various items. Its function is adds a touch of countryside charm to the overall environment and is an excellent decoration for any room. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [21], "output_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_51"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["provides support and comfort"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_52"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["generous", "Large"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_53"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_54"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["soft"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_55"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is vibrant green and white striped. Its texture is soft. Its material is cotton. Its size is generous. Its shape is square. Its placement is sits upright on the sofa. Its function is provides support and comfort. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_52"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["soft"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is vibrant green and white striped. Its material is cotton. Its size is generous. Its shape is square. Its placement is sits upright on the sofa. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is provides support and comfort. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_53"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["pillow"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is vibrant green and white striped. Its texture is soft. Its material is cotton. Its size is generous. Its shape is square. Its placement is sits upright on the sofa. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is provides support and comfort. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_54"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["vibrant green and white striped", "Green"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its texture is soft. Its material is cotton. Its size is generous. Its shape is square. Its placement is sits upright on the sofa. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is provides support and comfort. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_55"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_56"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["soft"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_57"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["likely cotton or similar material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_58"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["serve a decorative function, adding visual interest and comfort to the seating area"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_59"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is green and white. Its texture is soft. Its material is likely cotton or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its placement is leaning against the armrest. Its state is good condition. Its function is serve a decorative function, adding visual interest and comfort to the seating area. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_56"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["serve a decorative function, adding visual interest and comfort to the seating area"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is green and white. Its texture is soft. Its material is likely cotton or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against the armrest. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_57"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["green and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its texture is soft. Its material is likely cotton or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against the armrest. Its state is good condition. Its function is serve a decorative function, adding visual interest and comfort to the seating area. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_58"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["likely cotton or similar material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is pillow. Its color is green and white. Its texture is soft. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against the armrest. Its state is good condition. Its function is serve a decorative function, adding visual interest and comfort to the seating area. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_59"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_60"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_61"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["lying flat"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_62"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["pristine"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_63"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["pristine"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is keyboard. Its color is black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat. Its function is facilitates typing. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_60"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["black and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is keyboard. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat. Its state is pristine. Its function is facilitates typing. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_61"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is keyboard. Its color is black and white. Its material is plastic. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat. Its state is pristine. Its function is facilitates typing. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_62"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["lying flat"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["keyboard"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is keyboard. Its color is black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is pristine. Its function is facilitates typing. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_63"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["reddish-brown top, silver bottom", "Brown"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_64"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standing vertically on light-colored tile floor", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_65"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sturdy and durable", "Metal"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_66"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_67"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rack. Its color is reddish-brown top, silver bottom. Its material is sturdy and durable. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on light-colored tile floor. Its state is good condition. Its function is suitable for holding various items. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_64"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["suitable for holding various items"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rack. Its color is reddish-brown top, silver bottom. Its material is sturdy and durable. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on light-colored tile floor. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_65"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["sturdy and durable", "Metal"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rack. Its color is reddish-brown top, silver bottom. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on light-colored tile floor. Its state is good condition. Its function is suitable for holding various items. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_66"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rack"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["rack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is reddish-brown top, silver bottom. Its material is sturdy and durable. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on light-colored tile floor. Its state is good condition. Its function is suitable for holding various items. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_67"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["wood or plywood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_68"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["vertical", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_69"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_70"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_71"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is case. Its color is white. Its material is wood or plywood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is in good condition. Its function is storage cabinet or door. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_68"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is case. Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood or plywood. Its size is moderate. Its placement is vertical. Its state is in good condition. Its function is storage cabinet or door. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_69"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wood or plywood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is case. Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is in good condition. Its function is storage cabinet or door. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_70"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["case"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood or plywood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is in good condition. Its function is storage cabinet or door. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_71"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["vertical", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [10, 28], "object_names": ["sign", "rack"], "question": "choose the sign that is lying on the rack. What is shape of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["vertical", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, choose the sign that is on the right of it. What is shape of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["fixed to wall with two screws", "Hanging"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the sign that is on the right side of the couch. What is placement of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["good condition, no signs of wear or damage"], "object_ids": [7, 27], "object_names": ["pillow", "keyboard"], "question": "facing the front of the keyboard, select the pillow that is on the right side of it. What is state of the pillow ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, choose the sign that is on the right of it. What is material of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 27], "object_names": ["pillow", "keyboard"], "question": "looking at the front of the keyboard, choose the pillow that is to the right of it. What is size of the pillow ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["fixed to wall with two screws", "Hanging"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, choose the sign that is to the right of it. What is placement of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, choose the sign that is on the right of it. What is material of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [13, 5], "object_names": ["pillow", "picture"], "question": "the pillow that is far from the picture. What is size of the pillow ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["fixed to wall with two screws", "Hanging"], "object_ids": [10, 5], "object_names": ["sign", "picture"], "question": "select the sign that is close to the picture. What is placement of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [10, 8], "object_names": ["sign", "rail"], "question": "choose the sign that is far from the rail. What is size of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the sign that is to the right of the couch. What is material of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["likely cotton or similar material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 27], "object_names": ["pillow", "keyboard"], "question": "facing the front of the keyboard, select the pillow that is on the right of it. What is material of the pillow ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the sign that is on the right side of the couch. What is color of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [10, 16], "object_names": ["sign", "table"], "question": "the sign that is close to the table. What is material of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["cotton or similar material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [13, 27], "object_names": ["pillow", "keyboard"], "question": "find the pillow that is far away from the keyboard. What is material of the pillow ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [10, 6], "object_names": ["sign", "shelf"], "question": "choose the sign that is close to the shelf. What is size of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [10, 14], "object_names": ["sign", "couch"], "question": "find the sign that is near the couch. What is state of the sign ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10], "output_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the case and the counter are both Furniture"], "object_ids": [31, 15], "object_names": ["case", "counter"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31, 15], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0], [3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the picture are both Decorations"], "object_ids": [18, 5], "object_names": ["object", "picture"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18, 5], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the object are both Study and office supplies"], "object_ids": [20, 12], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the rail and the sign are both Sanitary ware products"], "object_ids": [8, 10], "object_names": ["rail", "sign"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8, 10], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706], [1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the pillow is Decorations and the object is Study and office supplies"], "object_ids": [22, 12], "object_names": ["pillow", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [22, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the case is Furniture and the object is Study and office supplies"], "object_ids": [31, 20], "object_names": ["case", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31, 20], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the sign is Sanitary ware products and the object is Study and office supplies"], "object_ids": [10, 12], "object_names": ["sign", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10, 12], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the sign is Sanitary ware products and the counter is Furniture"], "object_ids": [10, 15], "object_names": ["sign", "counter"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10, 15], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16], [3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the pillow are both Green"], "object_ids": [20, 22], "object_names": ["object", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20, 22], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the rail and the sign are both Black"], "object_ids": [8, 10], "object_names": ["rail", "sign"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8, 10], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706], [1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the shelf and the case are both White"], "object_ids": [6, 31], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the rack and the pillow are both Brown"], "object_ids": [28, 13], "object_names": ["rack", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [28, 13], "input_bboxes": [[1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the object are both Transparent"], "object_ids": [9, 12], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the pillow and the object are both More than one color"], "object_ids": [7, 18], "object_names": ["pillow", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [7, 18], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the case is White and the pillow is Green"], "object_ids": [31, 22], "object_names": ["case", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31, 22], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Transparent and the rail is Black"], "object_ids": [12, 8], "object_names": ["object", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12, 8], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Transparent and the case is White"], "object_ids": [21, 31], "object_names": ["object", "case"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the shelf is White and the pillow is Brown"], "object_ids": [6, 13], "object_names": ["shelf", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 13], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is More than one color and the object is Green"], "object_ids": [18, 20], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18, 20], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the rail is Black and the object is Transparent"], "object_ids": [8, 12], "object_names": ["rail", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8, 12], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the shelf and the case are both Wood"], "object_ids": [6, 31], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the sign and the rack are both Metal"], "object_ids": [10, 28], "object_names": ["sign", "rack"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10, 28], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16], [1.6211317602582258, -0.8024547686324615, 0.08527076381227794, 0.1420664102227627, 0.9336135836452703, 0.09078636337045742, 1.570796326794898, 4.3092732493915306e-16, -1.5441119962657128e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the keyboard and the object are both Plastic"], "object_ids": [27, 12], "object_names": ["keyboard", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the object are both Glass"], "object_ids": [21, 9], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21, 9], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the pillow and the picture are both Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [13, 5], "object_names": ["pillow", "picture"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13, 5], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the counter is Metal and the object is Glass"], "object_ids": [15, 21], "object_names": ["counter", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [15, 21], "input_bboxes": [[3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_25"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Glass and the case is Wood"], "object_ids": [9, 31], "object_names": ["object", "case"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_26"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Glass and the sign is Metal"], "object_ids": [9, 10], "object_names": ["object", "sign"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 10], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_27"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the pillow is Fabric/Feather and the case is Wood"], "object_ids": [13, 31], "object_names": ["pillow", "case"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_28"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Fabric/Feather and the counter is Metal"], "object_ids": [18, 15], "object_names": ["object", "counter"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18, 15], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_29"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the pillow are both Rectangular"], "object_ids": [12, 23], "object_names": ["object", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12, 23], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_30"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the rail are both Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [21, 8], "object_names": ["object", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21, 8], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_31"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Rectangular and the rail is Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [12, 8], "object_names": ["object", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12, 8], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_32"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the rail is Cylindrical and the sign is Rectangular"], "object_ids": [8, 10], "object_names": ["rail", "sign"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8, 10], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706], [1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_33"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [20, 6], "object_names": [20, 6], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20, 6], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_34"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [7, 23], "object_names": [7, 23], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [7, 23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_35"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [16, 15], "object_names": [16, 15], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 15], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [3.2959289587238962, 1.8557021715883821, 0.4249547729440058, 0.6027792788298136, 0.857772, 0.8080830879599918, -2.748894150244357, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_36"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [10, 8], "object_names": [10, 8], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10, 8], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16], [3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_37"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [14, 31], "object_names": [14, 31], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [14, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_38"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [21, 27], "object_names": [21, 27], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_39"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": [0], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": [27], "question": "How many objects are similar to this object in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": [4], "object_ids": [12, 5, 9, 23, 29], "object_names": [12, 5, 9, 23, 29], "question": "How many objects are similar to this object in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": [2], "object_ids": [10, 15, 16], "object_names": [10, 15, 16], "question": "How many objects are similar to this object in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [10], "input_bboxes": [[1.6190587869161603, -0.7956272106216475, 1.129881099433899, 0.1986774, 0.922422, 2.10262, 1.5707963267948966, 5.562916328556972e-18, 1.1430388262764602e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the object are both Standing upright"], "object_ids": [21, 9], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [21, 9], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_40"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the pillow and the pillow are both Leaning"], "object_ids": [7, 23], "object_names": ["pillow", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [7, 23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_41"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the pillow and the keyboard are both Lying flat"], "object_ids": [13, 27], "object_names": ["pillow", "keyboard"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_42"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the rail and the picture are both Hanging"], "object_ids": [8, 5], "object_names": ["rail", "picture"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [8, 5], "input_bboxes": [[3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706], [-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_43"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the keyboard is Lying flat and the pillow is Leaning"], "object_ids": [27, 23], "object_names": ["keyboard", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27, 23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_44"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the pillow is Lying flat and the rail is Hanging"], "object_ids": [13, 8], "object_names": ["pillow", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [13, 8], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_45"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the keyboard is Lying flat and the object is Standing upright"], "object_ids": [27, 12], "object_names": ["keyboard", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_46"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the shelf is Leaning and the rail is Hanging"], "object_ids": [6, 8], "object_names": ["shelf", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 8], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [3.001422655913656, 0.7316354073412774, 3.521901099433899, 0.2304865514151112, 1.196972, 2.48308, -1.6971034191041872, -1.5707963267948966, 1.0517907311401706]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_47"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": ["8"], "object_ids": [9, 12, 15, 18, 20, 21, 22, 28, 31], "object_names": ["object", "object", "counter", "object", "object", "object", "pillow", "rack", "case"], "question": "How many other objects are the same as this object in the placement?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [6, 7, 23], "object_names": ["shelf", "pillow", "pillow"], "question": "How many other objects are the same as this object in the placement?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [13, 27], "object_names": ["pillow", "keyboard"], "question": "How many other objects are the same as this object in the placement?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [5, 8, 10], "object_names": ["picture", "rail", "sign"], "question": "How many other objects are the same as this object in the placement?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The couch placed on the pillow provides comfort and support when sitting."], "object_ids": [14, 7], "object_names": ["couch", "pillow"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [14, 7], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The couch is similar to other couch and adding it to the 'pillow' increases comfort."], "object_ids": [14, 13], "object_names": ["couch", "pillow"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [14, 13], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The pillow as a cushion on the couch could also be used for a quick nap."], "object_ids": [22, 14], "object_names": ["pillow", "couch"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [22, 14], "input_bboxes": [[-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["generous", "Large"], "object_ids": [22, 14], "object_names": ["pillow", "couch"], "question": "In the dining region, this couch and X have relationship in their function:The X as a cushion on the couch could also be used for a quick nap. What is the size of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [22, 14], "object_names": ["pillow", "couch"], "question": "In the dining region, this couch and X have relationship in their function:The X as a cushion on the couch could also be used for a quick nap. What is the state of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The pillow is placed on the couch to provide support for relaxing activities such as reading or watching TV."], "object_ids": [23, 14], "object_names": ["pillow", "couch"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [23, 14], "input_bboxes": [[-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["pillow"], "object_ids": [23, 14], "object_names": ["pillow", "couch"], "question": "In the dining region, this couch and X have relationship in their function:The X is placed on the couch to provide support for relaxing activities such as reading or watching TV. What is the type of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["green and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [23, 14], "object_names": ["pillow", "couch"], "question": "In the dining region, this couch and X have relationship in their function:The X is placed on the couch to provide support for relaxing activities such as reading or watching TV. What is the color of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The object object is placed on the table table, keeping it tidy and out of the way when not in use."], "object_ids": [9, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [9, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "In the dining region, this table and X have relationship in their function:The X object is placed on the table table, keeping it tidy and out of the way when not in use. What is the size of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [9, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "In the dining region, this table and X have relationship in their function:The X object is placed on the table table, keeping it tidy and out of the way when not in use. What is the color of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The \"object\" object is displayed on the \"table\" table, possibly as a decorative item or for easy access."], "object_ids": [18, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18, 16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [18, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "In the dining region, this table and X have relationship in their function:The \"X\" object is displayed on the \"table\" table, possibly as a decorative item or for easy access. What is the size of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["standing upright on table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [18, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "In the dining region, this table and X have relationship in their function:The \"X\" object is displayed on the \"table\" table, possibly as a decorative item or for easy access. What is the placement of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The table object placed on the object table indicates that it may be a book for reading or an item for display."], "object_ids": [16, 21], "object_names": ["table", "object"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 21], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The shelfcase is placed next to the caseshelf, indicating that it may contain items for activities carried out on the table, such as work materials or electronic equipment."], "object_ids": [6, 29], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 29], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["stores books, files, and other items"], "object_ids": [6, 29], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "In the dining region, this case and X have relationship in their function:The Xcase is placed next to the caseshelf, indicating that it may contain items for activities carried out on the table, such as work materials or electronic equipment. What is the function of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 29], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "In the dining region, this case and X have relationship in their function:The Xcase is placed next to the caseshelf, indicating that it may contain items for activities carried out on the table, such as work materials or electronic equipment. What is the size of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["Next to the shelf case, there might be a case shelf containing additional tools or documents for regular desk activities."], "object_ids": [6, 31], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 31], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "In the dining region, this case and X have relationship in their function:Next to the X case, there might be a case shelf containing additional tools or documents for regular desk activities. What is the size of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [6, 31], "object_names": ["shelf", "case"], "question": "In the dining region, this case and X have relationship in their function:Next to the X case, there might be a case shelf containing additional tools or documents for regular desk activities. What is the color of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The shelf picture is placed on the picture shelf, possibly for convenient display and enjoyment."], "object_ids": [6, 5], "object_names": ["shelf", "picture"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [6, 5], "object_names": ["shelf", "picture"], "question": "In the dining region, this picture and X have relationship in their function:The X picture is placed on the picture shelf, possibly for convenient display and enjoyment. What is the state of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["stores books, files, and other items"], "object_ids": [6, 5], "object_names": ["shelf", "picture"], "question": "In the dining region, this picture and X have relationship in their function:The X picture is placed on the picture shelf, possibly for convenient display and enjoyment. What is the function of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The table object is placed on the object table, keeping it neat and tidy, and not causing obstruction when not in use."], "object_ids": [16, 19], "object_names": ["table", "object"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 19], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The object object is stored on the table table, making it more convenient and easy to access when needed."], "object_ids": [20, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [20, 16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [20, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "In the dining region, this table and X have relationship in their function:The X object is stored on the table table, making it more convenient and easy to access when needed. What is the state of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["green"], "object_ids": [20, 16], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "In the dining region, this table and X have relationship in their function:The X object is stored on the table table, making it more convenient and easy to access when needed. What is the color of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["Belonging to the category of storage, these items are used to organize and store things together."], "object_ids": [29, 30, 31], "object_names": ["case", "case", "case"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 3 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["Belonging to the same category of literature and art, these objects create a cozy atmosphere to make the users feel comfortable."], "object_ids": [18, 19, 20, 21, 12, 27], "object_names": ["object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "keyboard"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 6 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [18, 19, 20, 21, 12, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["Belonging to the category of home furnishings, these objects provide comfort and cleanliness."], "object_ids": [6, 16, 14, 7, 13, 22, 23], "object_names": ["shelf", "table", "couch", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 7 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [6, 16, 14, 7, 13, 22, 23], "input_bboxes": [[-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The living area is designed to meet various needs such as relaxation, work, and socializing. The furniture layout aims to provide comfort, functionality, and aesthetic appeal."], "object_ids": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "object_names": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "question": "There is a living region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the location and function description of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.8660269238357943, 1.0004205095181327, 0.3335143844806011, 0.2627099562185765, 0.2545928622160996, 0.06404862990659572, -1.555599589052915, -3.722652510857834e-16, -1.4715962152389707e-16], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The layout appears to be an open design, with furniture strategically placed to divide the room into different functional areas without hindering circulation. Specific dimensions were not provided."], "object_ids": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "object_names": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "question": "There is a living region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the space layout and dimensions of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.8660269238357943, 1.0004205095181327, 0.3335143844806011, 0.2627099562185765, 0.2545928622160996, 0.06404862990659572, -1.555599589052915, -3.722652510857834e-16, -1.4715962152389707e-16], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The room features high ceilings and a blend of modern and rustic elements with exposed brick walls. Large windows allow ample natural light to fill the space, while the smooth, light-colored flooring complements the room's aesthetic."], "object_ids": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "object_names": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "question": "There is a living region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the doors, windows, walls, floors and ceilings of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.8660269238357943, 1.0004205095181327, 0.3335143844806011, 0.2627099562185765, 0.2545928622160996, 0.06404862990659572, -1.555599589052915, -3.722652510857834e-16, -1.4715962152389707e-16], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["Items like the soft pillow pillows on the couch couch add a sense of comfort and warmth. Decorative items and personal belongings are placed on the shelf shelves, adding character to the space."], "object_ids": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "object_names": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "question": "There is a living region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the soft fitting elements and decorative details of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.8660269238357943, 1.0004205095181327, 0.3335143844806011, 0.2627099562185765, 0.2545928622160996, 0.06404862990659572, -1.555599589052915, -3.722652510857834e-16, -1.4715962152389707e-16], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The room utilizes natural light from the large windows, as well as indoor lighting fixtures that are not visible in the provided images. The lighting design may be intended to create a warm and cozy atmosphere."], "object_ids": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "object_names": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "question": "There is a living region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the lighting design of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.8660269238357943, 1.0004205095181327, 0.3335143844806011, 0.2627099562185765, 0.2545928622160996, 0.06404862990659572, -1.555599589052915, -3.722652510857834e-16, -1.4715962152389707e-16], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The color scheme is neutral, complemented by the vibrant color of the pillow pillow, creating a balanced and modern appearance. The style theme seems to be a fusion of contemporary and industrial."], "object_ids": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "object_names": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "question": "There is a living region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the color matching and style theme of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.8660269238357943, 1.0004205095181327, 0.3335143844806011, 0.2627099562185765, 0.2545928622160996, 0.06404862990659572, -1.555599589052915, -3.722652510857834e-16, -1.4715962152389707e-16], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The exposed brick walls and other unique architectural features add texture and depth to the space, making it visually appealing and giving it a distinctive character."], "object_ids": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "object_names": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "question": "There is a living region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the special features of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 29, 30, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-3.986280005119023, -0.2797416114304869, 1.2307556448267452, 0.03216974558642108, 0.7911764082755274, 1.0134404060293103, 0.39269850334543577, 1.5700924586837754e-16, -6.162975822039155e-32], [-3.577717619745302, 0.6247903469004978, 0.7609200987866819, 0.5894130602694998, 1.486106, 1.49866, -1.1780978234494612, -8.271806125530277e-25, -2.1073424338879935e-08], [-2.2250259984227343, -0.6063550231164903, 0.6481892463753802, 0.20458436948705355, 0.5418937658203402, 0.5021116675016557, 0.8885225387112622, -0.0916934401913401, -0.4717418781190374], [-1.6488991760145302, 0.8432314934425256, 0.5679057096498024, 0.244274, 0.228776, 0.5562867795681934, -1.5707963267948961, -3.483264841954923e-16, 4.391101056444403e-17], [-3.228648160999158, 0.692083122495173, 1.585818337997201, 0.385964, 0.361766, 0.1953595228733953, -1.1780978234494603, -6.280369834735108e-16, -7.77156117237609e-16], [-0.9260555907955649, -0.6125401381820207, 0.6500126374282452, 0.27851403172371714, 0.5747254979024876, 0.5352293953820354, 2.379559335864155, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.5121583112581399], [-1.5554582842277278, -0.45825969972231617, 0.4281176462782178, 1.217649669309589, 2.27198, 0.770150829136309, 1.5824322709343668, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.491388583365311, 0.7527687823669309, 0.15694902142288727, 0.812628166136231, 1.2105247974368596, 0.3138978439779767, -1.5540392759192354, -3.7249441292869434e-16, -1.465785922634188e-16], [-1.8660269238357943, 1.0004205095181327, 0.3335143844806011, 0.2627099562185765, 0.2545928622160996, 0.06404862990659572, -1.555599589052915, -3.722652510857834e-16, -1.4715962152389707e-16], [-1.6374379088683215, 0.8460305924767217, 0.37745175496104516, 0.226352, 0.219982, 0.18213328894570746, -1.496046114800752, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.196000548797517, 0.6121472629757668, 0.33747558993738525, 0.34261965806923456, 0.5395455566947658, 0.0894026189930274, -1.6017154630645163, -1.824473229688302e-16, 2.5557892615419965e-16], [-1.914529818951813, 0.5600915640988879, 0.3206510869197079, 0.31407192491485353, 0.2494878379199852, 0.05756837497161786, -1.5771288158287853, 1.1785232299968758e-16, -3.224557993897398e-16], [-1.4291312117704873, 0.9247371668157893, 0.4312830994338989, 0.264136, 0.278226, 0.277986, -1.5707963267948961, 1.5399236609267528e-16, 3.063093980497677e-17], [-1.157244301273871, -0.4781521468049972, 0.567883148201471, 0.17695430786865318, 0.4744516811258258, 0.42272520420479187, 2.5085443106453433, -5.551115123125783e-17, -0.8027257708299843], [-2.1595555045461405, -0.3653032490280478, 0.5972418430374922, 0.11314375185847134, 0.518158, 0.4154087353695244, 0.8363344582796081, -1.1102230246251565e-16, -0.7345944593392267], [-2.9560349670624912, 0.8615988611432266, 0.23256223387626473, 0.1407895455112932, 0.392669274258252, 0.05481361832160619, 0.3926985033454351, 3.925231146709439e-16, 1.0205600981444541e-15], [-3.6233080676710574, 0.5662324059660094, 0.5770115481982352, 0.4600758624826251, 0.22914486990757738, 0.27440117456296226, -1.2033175887020588, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.5507101333635993, 0.5805149140331968, 0.8904746210290694, 0.4579938405444289, 0.4127619920430313, 0.27270397175318334, -1.2303103132735609, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.558053529748845, 0.5932688423117212, 1.2428307549997737, 0.4134239318652929, 0.38356970838061266, 0.28586548596917594, -1.2180256287220728, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["You will see picture and shelf these two items."], "object_ids": ["14", "5", "6"], "object_names": ["couch", "picture", "shelf"], "question": "What will I see when I walk through couch?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": ["14"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["You can get object on the table."], "object_ids": ["14", "19", "16"], "object_names": ["couch", "object", "table"], "question": "Where is it more convenient for me to get a book while sitting on the couch?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": ["14"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["You can stand by the table."], "object_ids": ["18", "16"], "object_names": ["object", "table"], "question": "Where is it more suitable for object to stand?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": ["18"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["Sitting on the couch will give a better view."], "object_ids": ["5", "14"], "object_names": ["picture", "couch"], "question": "Where can I see picture more intuitively if I want to see it?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": ["5"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I need to walk from the couch to the table."], "object_ids": ["19", "14", "16"], "object_names": ["object", "couch", "table"], "question": "What do I need in order to object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": ["19"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["You can start from the first layer from the bottom of shelf."], "object_ids": ["27", "6"], "object_names": ["keyboard", "shelf"], "question": "Where can I go to get the keyboard?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region10", "input_bboxes_id": ["27"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_12"}]